solar system is made up of one
star a handful of planets more
than a hundred moons millions of
rocky asteroids and billions of
comet
all these bodies revolve around
Sun because of the gravity of
the Sun gravity of the Sun is a
force that pulls the objects
toward the center of the Sun the
Sun is the only star in our
solar system
it is a huge ball of fire
shooting light and heat in all
directions
no living thing can survive
without the Sun all the planets
and the moon's use sun rays for
their light
there are eight planets in our
solar system
they are mercury
Venus
earth
Mars
Jupiter
Saturn
arenas
connection
Pluto was once the ninth planet
of our solar system but now it
is considered a dwarf planet
yeah
venus is the hottest planet of
the solar system
earth is the planet where we
live
it's the third planet from the
Sun after Mercury and Venus
earth is the fifth biggest
planet of the solar system but
all the planets are tiny in
comparison to the Sun
it takes 365 days to revolve
around the Sun earth looks blue
from space because it is mainly
covered by water
Earth has one there are many
planets that have more than one
moon the moon revolves around
the earth as well as the Sun it
takes the moon approximately 28
days to revolve around the earth
yeah
the moon light we see from Earth
is the light from the Sun
there are some small rocky
bodies in the solar system that
have been left over from the
formation of the planets
these are called asteroids
asteroids don't have enough
gravity to pull them into the
shape of a ball
most of them lie in between Mars
and Jupiter
it's our balls of rock and ice
the grow tails as they approach
the Sun
comets come from far away and
imaginary place at the edge of
the solar system as it moves
closer to the Sun the glowing
tales are visible
this comes heat up Jackson does
are expelled and trail behind
them
all the stars that shine in the
sky are like our Sun many solar
systems together form a galaxy
we live in the Milky Way galaxy
which is spiral in shape
many galaxies together make the
universe